<stringmods>
  <StringTable>
    <Language name="English">
	    <String _locid="34666">Cheap scout building with no attack.</String>
	    <String _locid="34667">Jungle Outpost</String>
	    <String _locid="34671">Jungle Outpost</String>
	    <string _locid="34388">Great Temple</string>
	    <string _locid="34389">Great Temple</string>
	    <string _locid="34387">Sacred temple of the Inca. Trickles wood over time automatically.</string>
	    <String _locid="80002" symbol="cStringCivRolloverInca">&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Civilization bonus:&lt;/color&gt;\nKancha Houses spawn 2 Llamas when built. Llamas can be tasked at the community plaza at a less efficient rate than villagers. Starts with a free Chasqui who can construct Tambos; powerful Trading Posts which villagers can garrison in, and receives an additional Chasquis every Age. Military units can garrison in Kallankas and Strongholds. Priestesses can convert enemies and work at the Community Plaza.\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique units:&lt;/color&gt;\nChasqui, Plumed Spearman, Chimu Runner, Jungle Bowman, Bolas Warrior, Huaraca, Maceman, Priestess and Chincha Raft.\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique buildings:&lt;/color&gt;\nKallanka, Stronghold, Kancha House and Tambo\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique ceremonies:&lt;/color&gt;\nMoon Ceremony and Supay Ceremony\n\nA vast South American empire known for the power of its walls and smart administration.</String>
	    <string _locid="80013">1 villager, 100 wood, 1 Fat Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="80014">2 villagers, 200 wood, 2 Fat Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="80015">3 villagers, 300 wood, 3 Fat Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="80016">6 villagers, 600 wood, 6 Fat Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="80019">1 Town Center Travois and 1 Builder Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="80020">1 Stronghold Travois, 1 Builder Travois, and +1 Stronghold built limit</string>
	    <string _locid="80021">2 Stronghold Travois and +2 Stronghold built limit</string>
	    <string _locid="80023">1 Farm Travois, Great Feast, and Harvest Ceremony</string>
	    <string _locid="80024">Forest Spirit Ceremony and 2 Cloud Forest Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="80025">2 Builder Travois, Earth Gift Ceremony, and Green Corn Ceremony</string>
	    <string _locid="80026">3 Builder Travois and Excessive Tribute</string>
	    <string _locid="80028">2 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80029">3 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="80030">4 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="80031">8 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="80077">Tambos are cheaper and stronger.</string>
	    <string _locid="80083">Ranged warrior who hurls bolas for a wide area of effect. The bola slows down enemies. Good against cavalry in melee.</string>
	    <string _locid="80095">Powerful hand infantry that inflicts armor-piercing splash damage with a large bludgeon. Good against buildings and infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80106">Anti-building shock infantry. Good against artillery and skirmishers.</string>
	    <string _locid="80107">Anti-building and anti-skirmisher shock infantry that deals melee damage from a distance.</string>
	    <string _locid="80124">TEAM livestock and pets move much more quickly. Healers, scouts, and civilians gain a reduced bonus.</string>
	    <String _locid="80138">Supports 12 population and spawns 2 Llamas when built.</String>
	    <String _locid="80139">Inca House that supports 12 population and spawns 2 Llamas when built.</String>
	    <string _locid="80365">Each Kancha House will do a one-time muster of 1 Villager.</string>
	    <string _locid="80347">Improves the speed and hitpoints of your War Chief. Additionally, your War Chief now resists against ranged damage.</string>
	    <string _locid="80349">Greatly increases the damage of your War Chief, especially to Heavy Cavalry and Shock Infantry. Additionally, your War Chief now inflicts area damage and gains the Swashbuckler attack.</string>
	    <string _locid="80438">Sends 24 Peruvian dogs and improves them in combat. Allows your Warchief and Kancha Houses to raise them. Additionally, you can train more Peruvian dogs.</string>
	    <string _locid="80445">Tambos and Chasqui generate trickles of Experience.</string>
	    <string _locid="80447">Villagers gather all Food faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="80453">Each military building (Kallankas, War Huts, and Strongholds) will do a one-time muster of 2 Macemen.</string>
	    <string _locid="80464">Villagers, Fishing Boats and Warships gather faster from animals and animal resources last longer.</string>
	    <string _locid="80477">Warships are cheaper and gather from fish much more quickly and whales somewhat more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="80480">Warships and Fishing Boats move fast like Chinchillas and take less time to train.</string>
	    <string _locid="80495">The Chancas send 9 Macemen and increase their damage against infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80498">The Chachapoyas send 17 Huaracas and increase their attack range.</string>

	    <string _locid="80507">The Colla send 17 Bolas Warriors and increase their ranged damage, especially against Cavalry and Shock Infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80520">Buildings gain increased line of sight and siege armor.</string>
	    <string _locid="80530">The Aymara send 5 Chasquis and greatly improve their hitpoints, speed, and line of sight. Chasquis now slow down nearby enemies and can enter stealth with no speed penalty. Increases the build limit for Chasquis.</string>
	    <string _locid="80547">Kallankas get more hitpoints, build faster, train units more quickly, and cost no coin. Increases build limit.</string>
	    <string _locid="80552">Trade Monopoly is available an age early and is free.</string>
	    <string _locid="80560">Doubles the effectiveness of Llamas at the Community Plaza. Additionally, Llamas are cheaper and move more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="140000">Cloud Forest Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="140001">Cloud Forest</string>
	    <string _locid="140002">4 Cloud Forest Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="150001">Ships 1 villager, 100 Wood and 1 Fattened Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="150002">Seasonal Labor I</string>
	    <string _locid="150003">Seasonal Labor I Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="150004">Ships 2 villagers, 200 Wood and 2 Fattened Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="150005">Seasonal Labor II</string>
	    <string _locid="150006">Seasonal Labor II Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="150007">Ships 3 villagers, 300 wood and 3 Fattened Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="150008">Seasonal Labor III</string>
	    <string _locid="150009">Seasonal Labor III Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="150010">Ships 6 villagers, 600 wood and 6 Fattened Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="150011">Seasonal Labor IV</string>
	    <string _locid="150012">Seasonal Labor IV Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="150050">2 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="150075">15 Mapuche Allies</string>
	        </Language>
  </StringTable>
</stringmods>
