<stringmods>
  <StringTable>
    <Language name="English">
	    <string _locid="31143">Elite villager</string>
	    <string _locid="31144">Hardy villager that gathers coin quickly, but other natrual resources more slowly. Armed with dynamite for a powerful splash attack. Good against infantry but weak against cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="33519">Great Temple</string>
	    <string _locid="33520">Great Temple of the Aztecs. Generates a large trickle of Gold over time.</string>
	    <string _locid="33521">Great Temple</string>
	    <string _locid="33523">SPC Aztec temple</string>
	    <String _locid="34666">Cheap scout building with no attack.</String>
	    <String _locid="34667">Jungle Outpost</String>
	    <String _locid="34671">Jungle Outpost</String>
	    <string _locid="34388">Great Temple</string>
	    <string _locid="34389">Great Temple</string>
	    <string _locid="34387">Sacred temple of the Inca. Trickles wood over time automatically.</string>
	    <string _locid="35000">Town Center attack increased, and you receive a shipment of 6 Minutemen for each Town Center and Fort you have built. This shipment arrives more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="35308">Longbowman range increased and they deal increased damage to Heavy Infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="35506">Crates of 400 Food</string>
	    <string _locid="35719">Chests of 1,200 Coin</string>
	    <string _locid="35870">12 Grenadiers</string>
	    <string _locid="36334">TEAM Dragoons can be trained in the Commerce Age. Also benefits Ruyters, Cavalry Archers, Rifle Riders, Musket Riders, Yabusame. For Indian, Aztec, Inca, Swedish and Chinese allies, it makes Zamburaks, Eagle Runner Knights, Bolas Warriors, Black Riders and the 'Ming' and 'Mongolian' Banner Armies train slightly faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="44079">Improves your War Chief in combat and enables him to train Pet Jaguars.</string>
	    <string _locid="44142">Hand Skirmisher</string>
	    <string _locid="44143">Stealthy noble armed with an obsidian sword. Good against light cavalry and heavy infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="44225">6 Coyote Runners</string>
	    <string _locid="44227">16 Coyote Runners</string>
	    <string _locid="44239">10 Otontin Slingers</string>
	    <string _locid="44247">10 Eagle Runner Knights</string>
	    <string _locid="44330">The priests of Xochipilli send 8 Puma Spearmen and greatly increases their hitpoints.</string>
	    <string _locid="44332">The priests of Xolotl send 8 Villagers and boost the gather rate for Farms and Estates by 10% and lets them construct buildings quicker.</string>
	    <string _locid="44334">The priests of Coatlicue send 6 Arrow Knights, boosts all Arrow Knight attacks and unlocks splash damage for their ranged attacks.</string>
	    <string _locid="44336">The priests of Tlaloc send 14 Eagle Runner Knights and boost all Eagle Runner Knights' range.</string>
	    <string _locid="44338">The High Priest of Huitzilopochtli sends 7 Skull Knights, unlocks the Obsidian Storm charged ability, and boosts their splash area of effect radius and damage.</string>
	    <string _locid="44340">The High Priest of Quetzalcoatl sends 7 Jaguar Prowl Knights and enables them to train Pet Jaguars and construct Military Buildings.</string>
	    <string _locid="44342">The High Priest of Tezcatlipoca sends a group of Pet Jaguars and enhances Pet Jaguars greatly in combat and lets you train more of them.</string>
	    <string _locid="45082">2 Pet Jaguars, Better War Chief Strike attack and improves the War Chief's hitpoints by 20%.</string>
	    <string _locid="45084">4 Pet Jaguars, Better War Chief Strike attack and improves the War Chief's hitpoints by 30%.</string>
	    <string _locid="45086">7 Pet Jaguars, Better War Chief Strike attack and improves the War Chief's hitpoints by 40%.</string>
	    <string _locid="45088">12 Pet Jaguars, Best War Chief Strike attack and improves the War Chief's hitpoints by 50%.</string>
	    <string _locid="45090">1 Warrior Priest and 1 War Hut Travois.</string>
	    <string _locid="45100">3 Skull Knights; -10% Skull Knight Train Time.</string>
	    <string _locid="45102">5 Skull Knights; -25% Skull Knight Train Time.</string>
	    <string _locid="45104">8 Skull Knights; -40% Skull Knight Train Time.</string>
	    <string _locid="45125">1 Warrior Priest and 2 Nobles Hut Travois.</string>
	    <string _locid="45127">2 Warrior Priests, 2 Nobles Hut Travois, and +5% Community Plaza Work Rate.</string>
	    <string _locid="45129">3 Warrior Priests, 3 Nobles Hut Travois, and +10% Community Plaza Work Rate.</string>
	    <string _locid="47138">All Farm and Estate upgrades available before the Imperial Age are researched.</string>

	    <string _locid="60806">Powerful Indian heavy musket infantry that has a large bonus versus cavalry at melee.</string>
	    <string _locid="72560">15 Semi-fattened Cows</string>
	    <string _locid="79923">Ages up very fast and allows Jungle Outposts to receive shipments</string>
	    <String _locid="80002" symbol="cStringCivRolloverInca">&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Civilization bonus:&lt;/color&gt;\nKancha Houses spawn 2 Llamas when built. Llamas can be tasked at the community plaza at a less efficient rate than villagers. Starts with a free Chasqui who can construct Tambos; powerful Trading Posts which villagers can garrison in, and receives an additional Chasqui every Age. Military units can garrison in Kallankas and Strongholds. Native Allies shipments are cheaper and arrive more quickly\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique units:&lt;/color&gt;\nChasqui, Plumed Spearman, Chimu Runner, Jungle Bowman, Bolas Warrior, Huaraca, Maceman, Warrior Priestess and Chincha Raft.\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique buildings:&lt;/color&gt;\nKallanka, Stronghold, Kancha House and Tambo\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique ceremonies:&lt;/color&gt;\nMoon Ceremony and Supay Ceremony\n\nA vast South American empire known for the power of its walls and smart administration.</String>
	    <string _locid="80008">Ages up very fast and allows Jungle Outposts to receive shipments</string>
	    <string _locid="80009">Ages up very fast and allows Jungle Outposts to receive shipments</string>
	    <string _locid="80010">Ages up very fast and allows Jungle Outposts to receive shipments</string>
	    <string _locid="80011">Ages up very fast and allows Jungle Outposts to receive shipments</string>
	    <string _locid="80013">1 villager, 100 wood, 1 Fat Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="80014">2 villagers, 200 wood, 2 Fat Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="80015">3 villagers, 300 wood, 3 Fat Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="80016">6 villagers, 600 wood, 6 Fat Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="80019">1 Town Center Travois and 1 Builder Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="80020">1 Stronghold Travois, 1 Builder Travois, and +1 Stronghold built limit</string>
	    <string _locid="80021">2 Stronghold Travois and +2 Stronghold built limit</string>
	    <string _locid="80023">1 Farm Travois, Great Feast, and Harvest Ceremony</string>
	    <string _locid="80024">Forest Spirit Ceremony and 2 Cloud Forest Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="80025">2 Builder Travois, Earth Gift Ceremony, and Green Corn Ceremony</string>
	    <string _locid="80026">3 Builder Travois and Excessive Tribute</string>
	    <string _locid="80028">2 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80029">3 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="80031">8 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="80077">Tambos are cheaper and stronger.</string>
	    <string _locid="80083">Ranged warrior who hurls bolas for a wide area of effect. The bola slows down enemies. Good against cavalry in melee.</string>
	    <string _locid="80095">Powerful hand infantry that inflicts armor-piercing splash damage with a large bludgeon. Good against buildings and infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80106">Anti-building shock infantry. Good against artillery and skirmishers.</string>
	    <string _locid="80107">Anti-building and anti-skirmisher shock infantry that deals melee damage from a distance.</string>
	    <string _locid="80122">2 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80124">TEAM livestock and pets move much more quickly. Healers, scouts, and civilians gain a reduced bonus.</string>
	    <string _locid="80126">6 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80132">Elite Warrior Priestess</string>
	    <string _locid="80133">INF Elite Warrior Priestess</string>
	    <string _locid="80134">Assassin healer</string>
	    <string _locid="80135">Elite Inca healer. Highly effective against mercenaries, Explorers, War Chiefs, and Monks and moderately effective against cavalry.</string>
	    <String _locid="80138">Supports 12 population and spawns 2 Llamas when built.</String>
	    <String _locid="80139">Inca House that supports 12 population and spawns 2 Llamas when built.</String>
	    <string _locid="80365">Receive a shipment of 1 villager for each Kancha House you have built.</string>
	    <string _locid="80344">TEAM 2 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80345">TEAM received 2 Warrior Priestesses.</string>
	    <string _locid="80346">3 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80347">Improves the speed and hitpoints of your War Chief. Additionally, your War Chief now resists against ranged damage.</string>
	    <string _locid="80369">Your War Chief now does greatly increased damage vs. cavalry and shock infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80438">Sends 24 Peruvian dogs and improves them in combat. Allows your Warchief and Kancha Houses to raise them. Additionally, you can train more Peruvian dogs.</string>
	    <string _locid="80441">Villager hitpoints and armor increased. Fishing Boats get less armor.</string>
	    <string _locid="80445">Tambos and Chasqui generate trickles of Experience.</string>
	    <string _locid="80447">Villagers gather all Food faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="80453">Receive a shipment of 2 Macemen for each military building you have built (Kallankas, War Huts, and Strongholds).</string>
	    <string _locid="80464">Villagers, Fishing Boats and Warships gather faster from animals and animal resources last longer.</string>
	    <string _locid="80470">Warrior Priestesses gain increased attack.</string>
	    <string _locid="80477">Warships are cheaper and gather from fish much more quickly and whales somewhat more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="80480">Warships and Fishing Boats move fast like Chinchillas and take less time to train.</string>
	    <string _locid="80495">The Chancas send 9 Macemen and increase their damage against infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80498">The Chachapoyas send 17 Huaracas and increase their attack range.</string>
	    <string _locid="80501">The Chincha ship 5 Chincha Rafts and increase their hitpoints.</string>
	    <string _locid="80507">The Colla send 17 Bolas Warriors and increase their ranged damage, especially against Heavy Cavalry and Heavy Shock Infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80520">Buildings gain increased line of sight and siege armor.</string>
	    <string _locid="80530">The Aymara send 5 Chasquis and greatly improve their hitpoints, speed, and line of sight. Chasquis now slow down nearby enemies and can enter stealth with no speed penalty. Increases the build limit for Chasquis by 5.</string>
	    <string _locid="80533">The Cajamarca send 13 Jungle Bowmen and improve their bonus damage against heavy infantry. Additionally, Jungle Bowmen gain additional damage on their ranged attack and poison.</string>
	    <string _locid="80547">Kallankas get more hitpoints, build faster, train units more quickly, and cost no coin. Increases build limit.</string>
	    <string _locid="80552">Trade Monopoly is available an age early and is free.</string>
	    <string _locid="80560">Doubles the effectiveness of Llamas at the Community Plaza. Additionally, you can now train Llamas and they move more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="80890">Red Guard</string>
	    <string _locid="80892">Turns your Explorer into a powerful melee Duelist and ships an additional one from the Home City alongside a canine companion and 4 Surgeons. Additionally, Duelists gain a Heal ability.</string>
	    <string _locid="80894">Red Guards now move more quickly, cost a lesser amount of wood to train instead of food and gold, and are upgraded to guard status.</string>
	    <string _locid="80898">Delivers 4 Frontier Blockhouse Wagons. Your Settlers become Red Guards (Veteran Skirmishers), who can construct Torps, Blockhouses, and Military Buildings.</string>
	    <string _locid="90360">8 Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91501" symbol="cStringCivRolloverSwedish">&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Civilization bonus:&lt;/color&gt;\nTrains Miners in addition to Settlers, with a reduced build limit for each. Torps replace houses and gather wood from nearby trees. Crates of Food are replaced by crates of Surströmming, which spawn with less food, but fatten over time. Jaeger and Black Rider mercenaries can always be recruited from the Tavern. All non-native mercenary shipments can be sent an infinite amount of times. Starts off with a Church Wagon.\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Royal guard units:&lt;/color&gt;Pikeman (Dalkarl) and Karabinier (Drabant)\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique units:&lt;/color&gt;\nMiner, Carolean, Leather Cannon and Karabinier\n\nThe Swedish Empire became one of the greatest in Europe through innovation in military tactics and logistics. Its artillery and cavalry charges dominated the battlefields, particularly during the Thirty Years War. Despite a relatively small population, the Swedes fielded some of the largest armies in Europe, partly through the recruitment of mercenaries.</string>
	    <string _locid="91506">Carolean</string>
	    <string _locid="91507">INF Carolean</string>
	    <string _locid="91508">Skirmisher</string>
	    <string _locid="91509">Swedish skirmisher with a powerful short-ranged attack. Can charge quickly with his sword equipped to counter heavy infantry. Good against Heavy Infantry and Light Cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="91516">5 Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91534">Karabinier</string>
	    <string _locid="91535">CAV Karabinier</string>
	    <string _locid="91536">Accurate mounted skirmisher with a long ranged attack. Good versus heavy infantry, light cavalry, and artillery. </string>
	    <string _locid="91537">Mounted skirmisher</string>
	    <string _locid="91538">Karabinier attack and hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="91539">Veteran Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91540">Karabinier attack and hitpoints greatly increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="91544">Veteran Karabinier</string>
	    <string _locid="91558">1 Military Wagon and 1 Advanced Arsenal Wagon</string>
	    <string _locid="91560">All technogies and improvements (including Age Ups) are 10% cheaper and research 10% more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="91573">Light affordable artillery that dies when it attacks, but does lots of damage to infantry and buildings.</string>
	    <string _locid="91574">TEAM Sends a wagon that transforms into a Torp to support more population and gather nearby resources. Villagers have increased yield from trees.</string>
	    <string _locid="91614">Pikemen and Halberdiers gain increased damage against Heavy Infantry, but take longer to be trained.</string>
	    <string _locid="91616">Jaegers and Black Riders can be hired from all military buildings and now cost a lesser amount of Wood to recruit instead of gold.</string>
	    <string _locid="91617">Savolax Mercenaries</string>
	    <string _locid="91626">Pikemen and Halberdiers gain the ability to charge for a brief speed boost.</string>
	    <string _locid="91627">Dalecarlian Offensive</string>
	    <string _locid="91628">Dalecarlian Offensive Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91633">Hand Infantry / Hand Cavalry Combat</string>
	    <string _locid="91634">Hand Infantry / Hand Cavalry Combat Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91635">TEAM All hand infantry and hand cavalry hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="91636">TEAM Hand Infantry / Hand Cavalry Hitpoints</string>
	    <string _locid="91637">TEAM Hand Infantry / Hand Cavalry Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91638">Grenadiers and Riflemen (Caroleans and Karabiniers) gain increased ranged damage. Grenadiers deal increased ranged damage to Heavy Infantry and Caroleans additionally deal increased ranged damage to Heavy Infantry and Light Cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="91641">TEAM Increases speed, hitpoints, and damage of all Ranged Cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="91644">The sturdy breed of Finnhorses improves the hitpoints of Hussars, Dragoons, and Karabiniers.</string>
	    <string _locid="91647">Carolean and Karabinier range and line-of-sight increased. Karabiniers additionally deal increased damage to light cavalry and Eagle Runner Knights.</string>
	    <string _locid="91650">Heavy Cannons, Horse Artillery, and Falconets take up one less population slot.</string>
	    <string _locid="91667">Your Explorer is upgraded to a powerful melee Duelist, giving him bonus damage, especially against heavy infantry, increased armor and health, splash damage, a powerful Heavy Strike ability, a melee charge ability, and a canine companion.</string>
	    <string _locid="91670">5 Leather Cannons</string>
	    <string _locid="91678">Delivers 1 Frigate. Frigates and Galleons no longer cost gold to train, but have an increased wood cost.</string>
	    <string _locid="91687">Delivers 4 Torp Wagons. Torps gain more hitpoints and a ranged attack.</string>
	    <string _locid="91691">Grenadiers and Caroleans gain greatly increased hitpoints.</string>
	    <string _locid="91694">Swedish Pikeman attack, armor, and hitpoints greatly increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="91699">4 Leather Cannons</string>
	    <string _locid="91700">Delivers 10 Jaegers.</string>
	    <string _locid="91701">Contract Hessian Jaegers</string>
	    <string _locid="91702">Contract Hessian Jaegers Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91703">Delivers 7 Black Riders</string>
	    <string _locid="91704">Contract Black Riders</string>
	    <string _locid="91705">Contract Black Riders Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91706">Delivers 9 Highlanders.</string>
	    <string _locid="91707">Contract Scottish Highlanders</string>
	    <string _locid="91708">Contract Scottish Highlanders Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91709">Delivers 4 Fusiliers.</string>
	    <string _locid="91710">Contract French Fusiliers</string>
	    <string _locid="91711">Contract French Fusiliers Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91712">Delivers 12 Swiss Pikemen.</string>
	    <string _locid="91713">Contract Swiss Pikemen</string>
	    <string _locid="91714">Contract Swiss Pikemen Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91715">Delivers 5 Landsknechts.</string>
	    <string _locid="91716">Contract Landsknechts</string>
	    <string _locid="91717">Contract Landsknechts Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91738">4 Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91739">5 Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91740">8 Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91741">10 Leather Cannons</string>
	    <string _locid="91744">Leather Cannons train faster and are cheaper.</string>
	    <string _locid="91752">Miners gather coin more quickly from mines and mines last longer for Miners, +1 Prospector Wagon.</string>
	    <string _locid="91754">Blueberries</string>
	    <string _locid="91755">Villagers gather from berries more quickly and bushes last longer. Läckert!</string>
	    <string _locid="91756">Blueberries Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91765">5 Jaegers</string>
	    <string _locid="91777">Artillery now deal increased area damage (area of affect damage cap raised), but they now deal less damage to cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="91783">Ships 2 Crates of Surströmming, which provide more Food over time up to double the initial crate capacity.</string>
	    <string _locid="91784">Crates of 200 Surströmming</string>
	    <string _locid="91789">All Hussars transform into Karabiniers and enables Karabiniers to be trained in the Commerce Age.</string>
	    <string _locid="91790">Tähtitarha</string>
	    <string _locid="91791">Tähtitarha</string>
	    <string _locid="91792">Hussars deal more damage, especially to foot archers and skirmishers.</string>
	    <string _locid="91849">5 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="101051">Powerful heavy cavalry with a power splash ranged attack. Good against light infantry and artillery.</string>
	    <string _locid="101301">5 Raiders</string>
	    <string _locid="101303">4 Lifidi Knights</string>
	    <string _locid="101304">3 Lifidi Knights</string>
	    <string _locid="101305">6 Lifidi Knights</string>
	    <string _locid="101306">4 Lifidi Knights</string>
	    <string _locid="102553">Armored cannoneer mercenary from Portugal who fires a heavy musket inflicting splash damage.</string>
	    <string _locid="102849">Lifidi Knights and Raiders train faster. Raiders deal more damage to Villagers and Lifidi Knights gain increased area damage radii, especially in trample mode.</string>
	    <string _locid="102881">Particularly fattened Cattle containing 750 Food.</string>
	    <string _locid="102896">Neftenyas gain additional hitpoints.</string>
	    <string _locid="102928">Javelin Rider armor and attack increased. Oromo Riders deal more damage, especially to skirmishers and foot archers.</string>
	    <string _locid="103313">The Fulani town of Gwandu sends 9 Fulani Archers and 4 Lifidi Knights.</string>
	    <string _locid="103347">Receive a shipment of 4 Villagers for each Palace you currently have built.</string>
	    <string _locid="110001" symbol="cStringCivRolloverAmericans">&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Civilization bonus:&lt;/color&gt;\nFederal states unlock two new cards per age and two Factory cards in Industrial Age. Shipments are earned more quickly and you receive a free XP crate with most shipments. Economic improvements from the Home City are more powerful, but you have a lower Settler build limit and cannot ship resource crates. Generals can build Forts instead of Town Centers. Levies can be called repeatedly from multiple buildings with a global cooldown. Military units slowly heal over time outside of combat. Starts with a Fattened Sheep, an XP crate, and a Homestead Wagon instead of resource crates. \n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;National guard units: &lt;/color&gt;Sharpshooters (Marksmen), Spur Riders (Rough Riders)\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique units:&lt;/color&gt;\nTexas Ranger, Gatling Gun, Ironclad, Minuteman, Regular, Sharpshooter, Sloop, State Militia, Spur Rider, Steamer\n\nThe "land of opportunity" provided ample land for Settlers to plunder, creating the famous melting pot of Western European identities. Expanding from militia forces skilled in skirmishing tactics and marksmanship to a professional army, the United States of America ensured its independence and impressive road to prosperity for the owner class.</string>
	    <string _locid="110009">Hardy Skirmisher with a powerful short-ranged splash attack.</string>
	    <string _locid="110013">Fragile skirmisher with a slow, but powerful long-ranged attack. Good against infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="110017">Fragile Musketeer with a powerful ranged attack. Armed with a bayonet to beat cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="110018">Texas Ranger</string>
	    <string _locid="110019">CAV Texas Ranger</string>
	    <string _locid="110020">Imperial Hulk</string>
	    <string _locid="110021">Elite Ranged Cavalry with a powerful carbine attack. Good against Artillery, Heavy Infantry, and Heavy Cavalry, but weak against Skirmishers and Dragoons.</string>
	    <string _locid="110037">Marksmen</string>
	    <string _locid="110038">Imperial Marksmen</string>
	    <string _locid="110039">Sharpshooter attack, hitpoints, and ranged armor increased</string>
	    <string _locid="110040">Veteran Sharpshooter</string>
	    <string _locid="110041">Marksman</string>
	    <string _locid="110042">Imperial Marksman</string>
	    <string _locid="110049">Guard Texas Ranger</string>
	    <string _locid="110050">Imperial Texas Ranger</string>
	    <string _locid="110051">Texas Ranger attack and hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="110052">Veteran Texas Ranger</string>
	    <string _locid="110053">Guard Texas Ranger</string>
	    <string _locid="110054">Imperial Texas Ranger</string>
	    <string _locid="110045">Regular attack and hitpoints increased and they deal more damage to Heavy Cavalry at range.</string>
	    <string _locid="110067">Immigration from the British Isles delivers 2 Homestead Wagons.</string>
	    <string _locid="110073">Freedom Cannons</string>
	    <string _locid="110074">Imperial Freedom Cannons</string>
	    <string _locid="110076">Imperial upgrade for Freedom Cannons.</string>
	    <string _locid="110078">Freedom Cannon</string>
	    <string _locid="110079">Imperial Freedom Cannon</string>
	    <string _locid="110100">4 State Militia</string>
	    <string _locid="110101">6 State Militia</string>
	    <string _locid="110102">10 State Militia</string>
	    <string _locid="110103">5 State Militia</string>
	    <string _locid="110104">6 Regulars</string>
	    <string _locid="110105">9 Regulars</string>
	    <string _locid="110106">8 Regulars</string>
	    <string _locid="110107">16 Regulars</string>
	    <string _locid="110108">9 Texas Rangers</string>
	    <string _locid="110111">12 Sharpshooters</string>
	    <string _locid="110112">TEAM 3 Gatling Guns</string>
	    <string _locid="110113">5 Gatling Guns</string>
	    <string _locid="110114">2 Gatling Guns</string>
	    <string _locid="110139">Nationalism</string>
	    <string _locid="110146">Gatling Guns no longer need to reload, but have reduced range.</string>
	    <string _locid="110166">Spanish immigration grants a moderate XP trickle and ships an outpost wagon. Outpost build limit increased by 1.</string>
	    <string _locid="110178">Plants the United States flag to provide line of sight! Flags cannot be planted near starting Town Centers, and only one flag can be planted at a time. Enemies can capture the flag at any time.</string>
	    <string _locid="110189">French immigration improves the gather rate of all of your Villagers and delivers 2 Coureur des Bois.</string>
	    <string _locid="110204">Irish immigration delivers 3 Settlers, 1 Homestead Wagon, and improves Settler gather rate on Mills.</string>
	    <string _locid="110209">Chinese immigration delivers 3 Fattened Goats. Livestock fatten more quickly and Settlers gather from them faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="110220">Swedish immigration delivers 4 Torp Wagons. Torps gain more hitpoints and a ranged attack. Additionally, Villagers gather all Wood faster and Trees last longer.</string>
	    <string _locid="110221">Boston Tea Party</string>
	    <string _locid="110222">Hulk. Advanced armored warship.</string>
	    <string _locid="110237">Mercenary and Outlaw hitpoints and attack greatly increased</string>
	    <string _locid="110271">Ships 1 Meeting House Wagon and provides your Meeting House with unique American improvements to research.\n • Adds: Washington's Legion\n • Adds: Pennsylvania Cavalry\n • Adds: Guerrillas</string>
	    <string _locid="110277">Ships 12 Veteran Grenadiers equipped with Grenade Launchers.</string>
	    <string _locid="110278">Washington's Legion</string>
	    <string _locid="110279">Ships 1 Native Embassy Travois and allies you with the Tuscarora (Native Haudenosaunee) at your Native Embassy where some of their upgrades and units are available.</string>
	    <string _locid="110280">Tuscarora Allies</string>
	    <string _locid="110281">Receive and additional 2 XP crates with each shipments. Additionally, all shipments arrive faster, including this one.</string>
	    <string _locid="110283">Ships 2 Military Wagons, 2 Homestead Wagons, and 2 Outpost Wagons.</string>
	    <string _locid="110290">Ships 1 State Capitol Wagon and its improvements are cheaper and research more quickly (Excluding Spies and Blockade).\n • State Capitol, Oregon Trail, Statehood: -40% Cost and Research Time.\n • Capitol Improvements: -10% Cost and Research Time.</string>
	    <string _locid="110294">This Shipment arrives more quickly. Houses spawn a Minuteman when built and when destroyed by enemies. Minutemen retain their hitpoints 75% longer.</string>
	    <string _locid="110296">Ships 1 Turkey Scout and Villagers gather Food more quickly. All existing Town Centers spawn 3 Pilgrims.</string>
	    <string _locid="110300">Improves Settler speed and line of sight and speed. Natural resources last 25% longer.</string>
	    <string _locid="110302">Ships 2 Outpost Wagons. All existing and newly constructed Outposts spawn 1 State Militia and 1 Coureur while supporting +5 population.</string>
	    <string _locid="110304">Ships 6 State Militia and enables them to construct Military Buildings and place down an Inspiring Flag.</string>
	    <string _locid="110306">Gatling Guns are now Stealthy and have slightly increased movement speed.</string>
	    <string _locid="110316">Ships 2 Sharpshooters and 2 Deer for each shipment you have sent so far this game.</string>
	    <string _locid="110318">Ships 5 Coureurs and 5 Elite Cree Trackers.</string>
	    <string _locid="110320">Factories have more hitpoints and generate more resources.</string>
	    <string _locid="110326">Ship an Ironclad containing 4 Nitro Petards.</string>
	    <string _locid="110328">Ships 14 Zouave mercenaries.</string>
	    <string _locid="110330">Ships 4 Li'l Bombards and allows you to train them from the Saloon.</string>
	    <string _locid="110334">Fishing Boats are cheaper, train more quickly, and move faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="110336">Delivers 2 State Militia for each Mill and Estates you have currently built. Mills and Estates support +5 population.</string>
	    <string _locid="110338">Estates are cheaper and have all improvements researched.\n • All coin incomes are slightly improved.</string>
	    <string _locid="110342">Delivers 2 Homestead Wagons and buildings grant double XP when built. This bonus is retroactive for all buildings you have constructed this game.</string>
	    <string _locid="110344">Ships an additional Dragoon for each shipment you have sent so far this game. All units and technologies train and research slightly faster (+10%).</string>
	    <string _locid="110350">Ships an additional General and enables him for the rest of the game. Also, you can build a second Inspiring Flag and their line of Sight is increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="110352">Heavy Cavalry attack, hitpoints and movement speed increased.\n • ALL Cavalry train faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="110353">Florida Cracker Horses</string>
	    <string _locid="110354">Ships a Fattened Cow for each shipment you have sent so far this game.</string>
	    <string _locid="110374">Ships 2 Fort Wagons and increases Fort build limit by 2.</string>
	    <string _locid="110376">When destroyed by enemies, your Forts spawn 8 Minutemen and your Outposts spawn 2 Minutemen. Additionally, you can construct more Outposts and an additional Fort.</string>
	    <string _locid="110378">Ships 1 Gold Prospector Wagon and 8 Miners.</string>
	    <string _locid="110384">Uprising! Delivers an army of Pet Bears and Villagers become Revolutionaries.</string>
	    <string _locid="110409">Improves your United States General in combat, and makes him deadly to Mercenaries, Outlaws, and Treasure Guardians. Additionally, Treasure Guardians and enemy Mercenaries and Outlaws now yield Gold instead of XP when killed.</string>
	    <string _locid="110411">Ships 12 Texas Rangers.</string>
	    <string _locid="110412">Walker's Rangers</string>
	    <string _locid="110413">Increases the range of Sharpshooters and enables them to be trained in the Commerce Age.</string>
	    <string _locid="110414">Professionals</string>
	    <string _locid="110415">Greatly increases the attack of ranged infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="110417">Greatly increases the hitpoints of cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="110419">Ships an Ironclad containing Regulars. Enables an additional Ironclad to be constructed.</string>
	    <string _locid="110431">Ships 8 Magyar Hussars.</string>
	    <string _locid="110451">Saloons train units more quickly and now act as Home City shipment points. Additionally, Saloons support 25 population and can be constructed in the Exploration Age. Saloon Build Limit increased by 2 and Military Wagons can now build Saloons.</string>
	    <string _locid="110453">Villagers gather wood faster and trees last longer.\n • Villager: Gather Work Rate for Tree and Grove +25%; Tree Yield +25%</string>
	    <string _locid="110455">Delivers 2 Homestead Wagons. Villagers gather food from Mills faster.\n • Villager: Gather Work Rate for Mill, Farm, Rice Paddy, Field +30%</string>
	    <string _locid="110467">The next Federal State you research, or are researching, will Age Up 50 seconds faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="110483">Delivers 12 Polar Bears which will fight your enemies. All currently existing Town Centers spawn 1 Silver Prospector Wagon, which can open a Silver Mine.</string>
	    <string _locid="110484">Alaska Purchase</string>
	    <string _locid="110487">Ships 5 Sharpshooters and 5 Cree Trackers. Also upgrades Sharpshooters to Marksmen and Cree Trackers to Champion and allows you to train Trackers from the Native Embassy.</string>
	    <string _locid="110489">Ships 15 Elite Seminole Sharktooth Guerrillas, who are good against infantry and buildings.</string>
	    <string _locid="110490">Captured Seminole Guerrillas</string>
	    <string _locid="110504">TEAM Explorer Line of Sight is greatly increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="110527">Ships 2 State Militia and 5 Regulars and researches their Veteran upgrades.</string>
	    <string _locid="110542">Ironclads and Steamers gain increased armor. Additionally, they no longer cost Wood to construct, but now require a greater amount of Gold instead.</string>
	    <string _locid="110562">Slightly increases the attack and hitpoints of all military units. Additionally, Units heal outside of combat more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="110576">Artillery have more hit points and are trained faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="110595">Outlaws gain increased hitpoints and attack. Owlhoots gain increased range.</string>
	    <string _locid="110596">Road Agents</string>
	    <string _locid="110599">Ships 10 Gunslingers and 12 Pet Cougars. Enables Generals, Gunslingers, and Town Centers to retrain Pet Cougars.</string>
	    <string _locid="110618">Settlers gather Food 10% more quickly</string>
	    <string _locid="110619">1 Blockhouse Wagon</string>
	    <string _locid="110620">1 Blockhouse Wagon</string>
	    <string _locid="110626">Settlers gather Wood 25% more quickly and Trees last 25% longer</string>
	    <string _locid="110627">Settlers gather Wood 25% more quickly and Trees last 25% longer</string>
	    <string _locid="110631">Pine Tree State researched</string>
	    <string _locid="110632">Pine Tree State researched</string>
	    <string _locid="220000">3 Miners</string>
	    <string _locid="220001">4 Miners</string>
	    <string _locid="220002">10 Miners +1 Prospector Wagon</string>
	    <string _locid="220003">TEAM 3 Miners</string>
	    <string _locid="220004">TEAM 3 Miners Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="220005">Crates of 500 Surströmming</string>
	    <string _locid="220006">Ships 5 Crates of Surströmming, which provide more Food over time up to double the initial crate capacity.</string>
	    <string _locid="220007">Crates of 800 Surströmming</string>
	    <string _locid="220008">Ships 8 Crates of Surströmming, which provide more Food over time up to double the initial crate capacity.</string>
	    <string _locid="220009">Crates of 1300 Surströmming</string>
	    <string _locid="220010">Ships 13 Crates of Surströmming, which provide more Food over time up to double the initial crate capacity.</string>
	    <string _locid="220011">Crates of 300 Surströmming</string>
	    <string _locid="220012">Ships 6 Hessian Jaegers.</string>
	    <string _locid="220013">6 Jaegers</string>
	    <string _locid="220014">Ships 4 German Black Riders.</string>
	    <string _locid="220015">4 Black Riders</string>
	    <string _locid="220016">Delivers 7 Stradiots.</string>
	    <string _locid="220017">Contract Balkan Stradiots</string>
	    <string _locid="220018">Ships 8 Settlers and 2 Homestead Wagons.</string>
	    <string _locid="220019">Fäderneslandet</string>
	    <string _locid="220020">Ships 30 Vikings (Longbowmen) from the frozen wastes.</string>
	    <string _locid="220021">Vikings</string>
	    <string _locid="220022">Viking</string>
	    <string _locid="220023"> TEAM Ships 5 Crates of Surströmming, which provide more Food over time up to double the initial crate capacity.</string>
	    <string _locid="220026">Leather Cannon Hitpoints</string>
	    <string _locid="220027">Leather Cannon hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="220028">Leather Cannon Hitpoints Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="220029">Pikeman Charge</string>
	    <string _locid="220030">All Pikemen gain a brief speed boost.</string>
	    <string _locid="220031">Pikeman Charge time remaining</string>
	    <string _locid="220032">Halberdier Charge</string>
	    <string _locid="220033">All Halberdiers gain a brief speed boost.</string>
	    <string _locid="220034">Halberdier Charge time remaining</string>
	    <string _locid="220035">Hero Charge</string>
	    <string _locid="220036">Your Explorer and his pet gain a brief speed boost.</string>
	    <string _locid="220037">Hero Charge time remaining</string>
	    <string _locid="220038">TEAM Villager Siege</string>
	    <string _locid="220039">TEAM Villagers gain greatly increased siege damage.</string>
	    <string _locid="220040">TEAM Villager Siege Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="220041">Tatar Bolshevik</string>
	    <string _locid="220042">Soviet Allies</string>
	    <string _locid="220043">All Hussars are upgraded into Guard Bashkirs if not already. Ships 10 Guard Tatar Bolsheviks (Cavalry Archers) and allows you to train them. Unlocks shipments of Bashkirs and Tatar Bolsheviksfrom the Home City.</string>
	    <string _locid="220044">8 Tatar Bolsheviks</string>
	    <string _locid="220045">8 Bashkir Ponies</string>
	    <string _locid="220046">Proletarian</string>
	    <string _locid="220047">Ships 6 Miners and 1 Prospector Wagon and enables Miners and Proletarians at the Town Center.</string>
	    <string _locid="220048">Dictatorship of The Proletariat</string>
	    <string _locid="220049">Bombard Mode. Leather Cannons will take damage each time they fire a shot.</string>
	    <string _locid="220050">Fishmongers</string>
	    <string _locid="220051">Surströmming crates fatten more quickly and markets now slowly spawn crates of Surströmming, but you can now only have up to 3 markets built and they cost more.</string>
	    <string _locid="220052">Svenska Kyrkan</string>
	    <string _locid="220053">Ships an Advanced Church Wagon, increases Church build limit by 1, researches Mission Fervor, and unlocks powerful new technologies for the church.</string>
	    <string _locid="220054">Merchants</string>
	    <string _locid="220055">Deposits a large amount of XP and Shipments arrive more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="220056">3 Leather Cannons</string>
	    <string _locid="220057">Pilgrimage</string>
	    <string _locid="220058">Emigration</string>
	    <string _locid="220059">Delivers 8 Settlers.</string>
	    <string _locid="220060">Tithes</string>
	    <string _locid="220061">While working, each villager will trickle a small amount of coin.</string>
	    <string _locid="220062">Lookouts</string>
	    <string _locid="220063">Unit and building line of sight increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="220064">Swedish Alder</string>
	    <string _locid="220065">All present Torps spawn a tree.</string>
	    <string _locid="240000">Cloud Forest Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="240001">Cloud Forest</string>
	    <string _locid="240002">4 Cloud Forest Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="240050">Paititi</string>
	    <string _locid="240051">Jungle Outposts gain greatly increased hitpoints and line of sight.</string>
	    <string _locid="250001">Ships 1 villager, 100 Wood and 1 Fattened Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="250002">Seasonal Labor I</string>
	    <string _locid="250003">Seasonal Labor I Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="250004">Ships 2 villagers, 200 Wood and 2 Fattened Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="250005">Seasonal Labor II</string>
	    <string _locid="250006">Seasonal Labor II Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="250007">Ships 3 villagers, 300 wood and 3 Fattened Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="250008">Seasonal Labor III</string>
	    <string _locid="250009">Seasonal Labor III Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="250010">Ships 6 villagers, 600 wood and 6 Fattened Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="250011">Seasonal Labor IV</string>
	    <string _locid="250012">Seasonal Labor IV Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="250050">2 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="250051">5 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="250075">15 Mapuche Allies</string>
	    <string _locid="250500">Champion Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="250501">Warrior Priestess attack and hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="250502">Champion Warrior Priestess</string>
	    <string _locid="250503">Legendary Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="250504">Warrior Priestess attack and hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="250505">Legendary Warrior Priestess</string>
	    <string _locid="250750">Willaq Umu Support</string>
	    <string _locid="250751">The Willaq Umu sends 9 Warrior Priestesses and increases their hitpoints.</string>
	    <string _locid="250752">Willaq Umu Support Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="250999">4 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="260000">Increases the attack of all ranged infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="260001">Increases the hitpoints of all cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="260002">TEAM 7 Semi-Fattened Cows</string>
	    <string _locid="260003">Hire French Napoleon Guns</string>
	    <string _locid="260004">Ships 5 French Napoleon Guns.</string>
	    <string _locid="260005">Imperialism</string>
	    <string _locid="260006">The highest stage of Capitalism unlocks a medium gold trickle for the rest of the game.</string>
	    <string _locid="260007">TEAM Socialism</string>
	    <string _locid="260008">TEAM The creation of a workers' state unlocks a medium gold trickle for the rest of the game.</string>
	    <string _locid="260009">Hire French Zouaves</string>
	    <string _locid="260010">Ships 9 French Zouave mercenaries.</string>
	    <string _locid="260011">USA Furrier Bonus</string>
	    <string _locid="260012">Scatterguns</string>
	    <string _locid="260013">State Militia gain increased splash area of effect damage and radius, but reduced range.</string>
	    <string _locid="260014">Bourbon Distillery</string>
	    <string _locid="260015">Federal Reserve</string>
	    <string _locid="260016">Oneida Allies</string>
	    <string _locid="260017">The Oneida send 6 Rams and 5 Mantlets.</string>
	    <string _locid="260018">Spur Rider</string>
	    <string _locid="260019">CAV Spur Rider</string>
	    <string _locid="260020">Heavy Cavalry</string>
	    <string _locid="260021">Durable Heavy Cavalry with low damage. Good against Artillery, Skirmishers, and Foot Archers.</string>
	    <string _locid="260022">6 Texas Rangers</string>
	    <string _locid="260023">9 Texas Rangers</string>
	    <string _locid="260024">Veteran Spur Riders</string>
	    <string _locid="260025">Rough Riders</string>
	    <string _locid="260026">Imperial Rough Riders</string>
	    <string _locid="260027">Spur Rider attack and hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="260028">Spur Rider attack, hitpoints, and ranged armor increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="260029">Imperial upgrade for Rough Riders</string>
	    <string _locid="260030">Veteran Spur Rider</string>
	    <string _locid="260031">Rough Rider</string>
	    <string _locid="260032">Imperial Rough Rider</string>
	    <string _locid="260033">200 XP Crates with every shipment</string>
	    <string _locid="260034">Guerrillas</string>
	    <string _locid="260035">Infantry have increased attack, but have reduced hitpoints.</string>
	    <string _locid="260036">Lower cooldown Conscription if Minutemen Companies has been sent.</string>
	    <string _locid="260037">Rockets' Red Glare</string>
	    <string _locid="260038">Rockets and Mortars deal increased damage to buildings.</string>
	    <string _locid="260039">5 Homestead Wagons</string>
	    <string _locid="260040">Delivers 5 Homestead Wagons, which transform into Mills, Estates, Houses, Docks, Markets, or Livestock Pens</string>
	    <string _locid="260041">TEAM 4 Texas Rangers</string>
	    <string _locid="260042">Delivers a Wild Turkey Scout. Also, Villagers gather Coin from Estates and Rice Paddies faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="260043">Brass Beasts</string>
	    <string _locid="260044">Gatling Guns gain additional ranged and siege armor.</string>
	    <string _locid="260045">5 Warrior Priests</string>
	    <string _locid="260046">All Shock Infantry train faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="260047">Cacao Cultivation</string>
	    <string _locid="260048">Villagers gather Coin from Estates faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="260047">Flower Wars</string>
	    <string _locid="260048">Ships an additional War Chief and enables him for the rest of the game. Their auras do not stack.</string>
	    <string _locid="260049">John Brown</string>
	    <string _locid="260050">Chicomecoatl Worship</string>
	    <string _locid="260051">Receive a small trickle of Wood for the rest of the game.</string>
	    <string _locid="260052">Tlaltecuhtli Worship</string>
	    <string _locid="260053">Receive a moderate trickle of Wood for the rest of the game.</string>
	</Language>
  </StringTable>
</stringmods>
