<stringmods>
  <StringTable>
    <Language name="English">
	    <string _locid="31143">Elite villager</string>
	    <string _locid="31144">Hardy villager that gathers coin quickly, but other natrual resources more slowly. Armed with dynamite for a powerful splash attack. Good against infantry but weak against cavalry.</string>
	    <String _locid="34666">Cheap scout building with no attack.</String>
	    <String _locid="34667">Jungle Outpost</String>
	    <String _locid="34671">Jungle Outpost</String>
	    <string _locid="34388">Great Temple</string>
	    <string _locid="34389">Great Temple</string>
	    <string _locid="34387">Sacred temple of the Inca. Trickles wood over time automatically.</string>
	    <string _locid="35000">Town Center attack increased, and you receive a shipment of 6 Minutemen for each Town Center and Fort you have built. This shipment arrives more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="35308">Longbowman range increased and they deal increased damage to Heavy Infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="35506">Crates of 400 Food</string>
	    <string _locid="35870">12 Grenadiers</string>
	    <string _locid="60806">Powerful Indian heavy musket infantry that has a large bonus versus cavalry at melee.</string>
	    <string _locid="79923">Ages up very fast and allows Jungle Outposts to receive shipments</string>
	    <String _locid="80002" symbol="cStringCivRolloverInca">&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Civilization bonus:&lt;/color&gt;\nKancha Houses spawn 2 Llamas when built. Llamas can be tasked at the community plaza at a less efficient rate than villagers. Starts with a free Chasqui who can construct Tambos; powerful Trading Posts which villagers can garrison in, and receives an additional Chasqui every Age. Military units can garrison in Kallankas and Strongholds. Native Allies shipments are cheaper and arrive more quickly\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique units:&lt;/color&gt;\nChasqui, Plumed Spearman, Chimu Runner, Jungle Bowman, Bolas Warrior, Huaraca, Maceman, Warrior Priestess and Chincha Raft.\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique buildings:&lt;/color&gt;\nKallanka, Stronghold, Kancha House and Tambo\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique ceremonies:&lt;/color&gt;\nMoon Ceremony and Supay Ceremony\n\nA vast South American empire known for the power of its walls and smart administration.</String>
	    <string _locid="80008">Ages up very fast and allows Jungle Outposts to receive shipments</string>
	    <string _locid="80009">Ages up very fast and allows Jungle Outposts to receive shipments</string>
	    <string _locid="80010">Ages up very fast and allows Jungle Outposts to receive shipments</string>
	    <string _locid="80011">Ages up very fast and allows Jungle Outposts to receive shipments</string>
	    <string _locid="80013">1 villager, 100 wood, 1 Fat Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="80014">2 villagers, 200 wood, 2 Fat Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="80015">3 villagers, 300 wood, 3 Fat Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="80016">6 villagers, 600 wood, 6 Fat Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="80019">1 Town Center Travois and 1 Builder Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="80020">1 Stronghold Travois, 1 Builder Travois, and +1 Stronghold built limit</string>
	    <string _locid="80021">2 Stronghold Travois and +2 Stronghold built limit</string>
	    <string _locid="80023">1 Farm Travois, Great Feast, and Harvest Ceremony</string>
	    <string _locid="80024">Forest Spirit Ceremony and 2 Cloud Forest Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="80025">2 Builder Travois, Earth Gift Ceremony, and Green Corn Ceremony</string>
	    <string _locid="80026">3 Builder Travois and Excessive Tribute</string>
	    <string _locid="80028">2 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80029">3 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="80031">8 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="80077">Tambos are cheaper and stronger.</string>
	    <string _locid="80083">Ranged warrior who hurls bolas for a wide area of effect. The bola slows down enemies. Good against cavalry in melee.</string>
	    <string _locid="80095">Powerful hand infantry that inflicts armor-piercing splash damage with a large bludgeon. Good against buildings and infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80106">Anti-building shock infantry. Good against artillery and skirmishers.</string>
	    <string _locid="80107">Anti-building and anti-skirmisher shock infantry that deals melee damage from a distance.</string>
	    <string _locid="80122">2 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80124">TEAM livestock and pets move much more quickly. Healers, scouts, and civilians gain a reduced bonus.</string>
	    <string _locid="80126">6 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80132">Elite Warrior Priestess</string>
	    <string _locid="80133">INF Elite Warrior Priestess</string>
	    <string _locid="80134">Assassin healer</string>
	    <string _locid="80135">Elite Inca healer. Highly effective against mercenaries, Explorers, War Chiefs, and Monks and moderately effective against cavalry.</string>
	    <String _locid="80138">Supports 12 population and spawns 2 Llamas when built.</String>
	    <String _locid="80139">Inca House that supports 12 population and spawns 2 Llamas when built.</String>
	    <string _locid="80365">Receive a shipment of 1 villager for each Kancha House you have built.</string>
	    <string _locid="80344">TEAM 2 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80345">TEAM received 2 Warrior Priestesses.</string>
	    <string _locid="80346">3 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="80347">Improves the speed and hitpoints of your War Chief. Additionally, your War Chief now resists against ranged damage.</string>
	    <string _locid="80369">Your War Chief now does greatly increased damage vs. cavalry and shock infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80438">Sends 24 Peruvian dogs and improves them in combat. Allows your Warchief and Kancha Houses to raise them. Additionally, you can train more Peruvian dogs.</string>
	    <string _locid="80441">Villager hitpoints and armor increased. Fishing Boats get less armor.</string>
	    <string _locid="80445">Tambos and Chasqui generate trickles of Experience.</string>
	    <string _locid="80447">Villagers gather all Food faster.</string>
	    <string _locid="80453">Receive a shipment of 2 Macemen for each military building you have built (Kallankas, War Huts, and Strongholds).</string>
	    <string _locid="80464">Villagers, Fishing Boats and Warships gather faster from animals and animal resources last longer.</string>
	    <string _locid="80470">Warrior Priestesses gain increased attack.</string>
	    <string _locid="80477">Warships are cheaper and gather from fish much more quickly and whales somewhat more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="80480">Warships and Fishing Boats move fast like Chinchillas and take less time to train.</string>
	    <string _locid="80495">The Chancas send 9 Macemen and increase their damage against infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80498">The Chachapoyas send 17 Huaracas and increase their attack range.</string>
	    <string _locid="80501">The Chincha ship 5 Chincha Rafts and increase their hitpoints.</string>
	    <string _locid="80507">The Colla send 17 Bolas Warriors and increase their ranged damage, especially against Heavy Cavalry and Heavy Shock Infantry.</string>
	    <string _locid="80520">Buildings gain increased line of sight and siege armor.</string>
	    <string _locid="80530">The Aymara send 5 Chasquis and greatly improve their hitpoints, speed, and line of sight. Chasquis now slow down nearby enemies and can enter stealth with no speed penalty. Increases the build limit for Chasquis.</string>
	    <string _locid="80533">The Cajamarca send 13 Jungle Bowmen and improve their bonus damage against heavy infantry. Additionally, Jungle Bowmen gain additional damage on their ranged attack and poison.</string>
	    <string _locid="80547">Kallankas get more hitpoints, build faster, train units more quickly, and cost no coin. Increases build limit.</string>
	    <string _locid="80552">Trade Monopoly is available an age early and is free.</string>
	    <string _locid="80560">Doubles the effectiveness of Llamas at the Community Plaza. Additionally, you can now train Llamas and they move more quickly.</string>
	    <string _locid="80890">Red Guard</string>
	    <string _locid="80892">Turns your Explorer into a powerful melee Duelist and ships an additional one from the Home City alongside a canine companion and 4 Surgeons. Additionally, Duelists gain a Heal ability.</string>
	    <string _locid="80894">Red Guards now move more quickly, cost a lesser amount of wood to train instead of food and gold, and are upgraded to guard status.</string>
	    <string _locid="80898">Delivers 4 Frontier Blockhouse Wagons. Your Settlers become Red Guards (Veteran Skirmishers), who can construct Torps, Blockhouses, and Military Buildings.</string>
	    <string _locid="90360">8 Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91501" symbol="cStringCivRolloverSwedish">&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Civilization bonus:&lt;/color&gt;\nTrains miners in addition to settlers. Torps replace houses and gather wood from nearby trees. Crates of Food are replaced by crates of Surströmming, which fatten over time. Jaeger and Black Rider mercenaries can always be recruited from the Tavern. All non-native mercenary shipments can be sent an infinite amount of times.\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Royal guard units:&lt;/color&gt;Pikeman (Dalkarl) and Karabinier (Drabant)\n&lt;color=1.0, 1.0, 0.0&gt;Unique units:&lt;/color&gt;\nMiner, Carolean, Leather Cannon and Karabinier\n\nThe Swedish Empire became one of the greatest in Europe through innovation in military tactics and logistics. Its artillery and cavalry charges dominated the battlefields, particularly during the Thirty Years War. Despite a relatively small population, the Swedes fielded some of the largest armies in Europe, partly through the recruitment of mercenaries.</string>
	    <string _locid="91506">Carolean</string>
	    <string _locid="91507">INF Carolean</string>
	    <string _locid="91508">Skirmisher</string>
	    <string _locid="91509">Swedish skirmisher with a powerful short-ranged attack. Can charge quickly with his sword equipped to counter heavy infantry. Good against Heavy Infantry and Light Cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="91516">5 Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91534">Karabinier</string>
	    <string _locid="91535">CAV Karabinier</string>
	    <string _locid="91536">Accurate mounted skirmisher with a long ranged attack. Good versus heavy infantry, light cavalry, and artillery. </string>
	    <string _locid="91537">Mounted skirmisher</string>
	    <string _locid="91538">Karabinier attack and hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="91539">Veteran Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91540">Karabinier attack and hitpoints greatly increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="91544">Veteran Karabinier</string>
	    <string _locid="91558">1 Military Wagon and 1 Advanced Arsenal Wagon</string>
	    <string _locid="91560">All technogies and improvements (including Age Ups) are cheaper and research more quickly</string>
	    <string _locid="91573">Light affordable artillery that dies when it attacks, but does lots of damage to infantry and buildings.</string>
	    <string _locid="91574">TEAM Sends a wagon that transforms into a Torp to support more population and gather nearby resources. Villagers have increased yield from trees.</string>
	    <string _locid="91614">Pikemen and Halberdiers gain increased damage against Heavy Infantry, but take longer to be trained.</string>
	    <string _locid="91616">Jaegers and Black Riders can be hired from all military buildings and now cost a lesser amount of Wood to recruit instead of gold.</string>
	    <string _locid="91617">Savolax Mercenaries</string>
	    <string _locid="91626">Pikemen and Halberdiers gain the ability to charge for a brief speed boost.</string>
	    <string _locid="91627">Dalecarlian Offensive</string>
	    <string _locid="91628">Dalecarlian Offensive Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91633">Hand Infantry / Hand Cavalry Combat</string>
	    <string _locid="91634">Hand Infantry / Hand Cavalry Combat Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91635">TEAM All hand infantry and hand cavalry hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="91636">TEAM Hand Infantry / Hand Cavalry Hitpoints</string>
	    <string _locid="91637">TEAM Hand Infantry / Hand Cavalry Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91638">Grenadiers and Riflemen (Caroleans and Karabiniers) gain increased ranged damage. Grenadiers deal increased ranged damage to Heavy Infantry and Caroleans additionally deal increased ranged damage to Heavy Infantry and Light Cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="91641">TEAM Increases speed, hitpoints, and damage of all Ranged Cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="91644">The sturdy breed of Finnhorses improves the hitpoints of Hussars, Dragoons, and Karabiniers.</string>
	    <string _locid="91647">Carolean and Karabinier range and line-of-sight increased. Karabiniers additionally deal increased damage to light cavalry and Eagle Runner Knights.</string>
	    <string _locid="91650">Heavy Cannons, Horse Artillery, and Falconets take up one less population slot.</string>
	    <string _locid="91667">Your Explorer is upgraded to a powerful melee Duelist, giving him bonus damage, especially against heavy infantry, increased armor and health, splash damage, a powerful Heavy Strike ability, a melee charge ability, and a canine companion.</string>
	    <string _locid="91670">5 Leather Cannons</string>
	    <string _locid="91678">Delivers 1 Frigate. Frigates and Galleons no longer cost gold to train, but have an increased wood cost.</string>
	    <string _locid="91687">Delivers 4 Torp Wagons. Torps gain more hitpoints, can receive Home City shipments and gather from wood crates.</string>
	    <string _locid="91691">Grenadiers and Caroleans gain greatly increased hitpoints.</string>
	    <string _locid="91694">Swedish Pikeman attack, armor, and hitpoints greatly increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="91699">4 Leather Cannons</string>
	    <string _locid="91738">4 Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91739">5 Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91740">8 Karabiniers</string>
	    <string _locid="91741">10 Leather Cannons</string>
	    <string _locid="91744">Leather Cannons train faster and are cheaper.</string>
	    <string _locid="91752">Miners gather coin more quickly from mines and mines last longer for Miners, +1 Prospector Wagon.</string>
	    <string _locid="91754">Blueberries</string>
	    <string _locid="91755">Villagers gather from berries more quickly and bushes last longer. Läckert!</string>
	    <string _locid="91756">Blueberries Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="91765">5 Jaegers</string>
	    <string _locid="91777">Artillery now deal increased area damage (area of affect damage cap raised), but they now deal less damage to cavalry.</string>
	    <string _locid="91783">Ships 2 Crates of Surströmming, which provide more Food over time up to double the initial crate capacity.</string>
	    <string _locid="91784">Crates of 200 Surströmming</string>
	    <string _locid="91789">All Hussars transform into Karabiniers and enables Karabiniers to be trained in the Commerce Age.</string>
	    <string _locid="91790">Tähtitarha</string>
	    <string _locid="91791">Tähtitarha</string>
	    <string _locid="91792">Hussars deal more damage, especially to foot archers and skirmishers.</string>
	    <string _locid="91849">5 Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="220000">3 Miners</string>
	    <string _locid="220001">4 Miners</string>
	    <string _locid="220002">10 Miners +1 Prospector Wagon</string>
	    <string _locid="220003">TEAM 3 Miners</string>
	    <string _locid="220004">TEAM 3 Miners Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="220005">Crates of 500 Surströmming</string>
	    <string _locid="220006">Ships 5 Crates of Surströmming, which provide more Food over time up to double the initial crate capacity.</string>
	    <string _locid="220007">Crates of 800 Surströmming</string>
	    <string _locid="220008">Ships 8 Crates of Surströmming, which provide more Food over time up to double the initial crate capacity.</string>
	    <string _locid="220009">Crates of 1300 Surströmming</string>
	    <string _locid="220010">Ships 13 Crates of Surströmming, which provide more Food over time up to double the initial crate capacity.</string>
	    <string _locid="220011">Crates of 300 Surströmming</string>
	    <string _locid="220012">Ships 6 Hessian Jaegers.</string>
	    <string _locid="220013">6 Jaegers</string>
	    <string _locid="220014">Ships 4 German Black Riders.</string>
	    <string _locid="220015">4 Black Riders</string>
	    <string _locid="220016">Delivers 10 Stradiots. Enables Stradiot hiring at military buildings.</string>
	    <string _locid="220017">Contract Balkan Stradiots</string>
	    <string _locid="220018">Ships 8 Settlers and 2 Homestead Wagons.</string>
	    <string _locid="220019">Fäderneslandet</string>
	    <string _locid="220020">Ships 30 Vikings (Longbowmen) from the frozen wastes.</string>
	    <string _locid="220021">Vikings</string>
	    <string _locid="220022">Viking</string>
	    <string _locid="220023"> TEAM Ships 5 Crates of Surströmming, which provide more Food over time up to double the initial crate capacity.</string>
	    <string _locid="220026">Leather Cannon Hitpoints</string>
	    <string _locid="220027">Leather Cannon hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="220028">Leather Cannon Hitpoints Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="220029">Pikeman Charge</string>
	    <string _locid="220030">All Pikemen gain a brief speed boost.</string>
	    <string _locid="220031">Pikeman Charge time remaining</string>
	    <string _locid="220032">Halberdier Charge</string>
	    <string _locid="220033">All Halberdiers gain a brief speed boost.</string>
	    <string _locid="220034">Halberdier Charge time remaining</string>
	    <string _locid="220035">Hero Charge</string>
	    <string _locid="220036">Your Explorer and his pet gain a brief speed boost.</string>
	    <string _locid="220037">Hero Charge time remaining</string>
	    <string _locid="220038">TEAM Villager Siege</string>
	    <string _locid="220039">TEAM Villagers gain greatly increased siege damage.</string>
	    <string _locid="220040">TEAM Villager Siege Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="220041">Tatar Bolshevik</string>
	    <string _locid="220042">Soviet Allies</string>
	    <string _locid="220043">All Hussars are upgraded into Guard Bashkirs if not already. Ships 10 Guard Tatar Bolsheviks (Cavalry Archers) and allows you to train them. Unlocks shipments of Bashkirs and Tatar Bolsheviksfrom the Home City.</string>
	    <string _locid="220044">8 Tatar Bolsheviks</string>
	    <string _locid="220045">8 Bashkir Ponies</string>
	    <string _locid="220046">Proletarian</string>
	    <string _locid="220047">Ships 6 Miners and 1 Prospector Wagon and enables Miners and Proletarians at the Town Center.</string>
	    <string _locid="220048">Dictatorship of The Proletariat</string>
	    <string _locid="220049">Bombard Mode. Leather Cannons will take damage each time they fire a shot.</string>
	    <string _locid="220050">Fishmongers</string>
	    <string _locid="220051">Surströmming crates fatten more quickly and markets now slowly spawn crates of Surströmming, but you can now only have up to 3 markets built..</string>
	    <string _locid="240000">Cloud Forest Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="240001">Cloud Forest</string>
	    <string _locid="240002">4 Cloud Forest Travois</string>
	    <string _locid="240050">Paititi</string>
	    <string _locid="240051">Jungle Outposts gain greatly increase hitpoints and line of sight.</string>
	    <string _locid="250001">Ships 1 villager, 100 Wood and 1 Fattened Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="250002">Seasonal Labor I</string>
	    <string _locid="250003">Seasonal Labor I Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="250004">Ships 2 villagers, 200 Wood and 2 Fattened Llamas</string>
	    <string _locid="250005">Seasonal Labor II</string>
	    <string _locid="250006">Seasonal Labor II Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="250007">Ships 3 villagers, 300 wood and 3 Fattened Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="250008">Seasonal Labor III</string>
	    <string _locid="250009">Seasonal Labor III Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="250010">Ships 6 villagers, 600 wood and 6 Fattened Llama</string>
	    <string _locid="250011">Seasonal Labor IV</string>
	    <string _locid="250012">Seasonal Labor IV Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="250050">2 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="250051">5 Macemen</string>
	    <string _locid="250075">15 Mapuche Allies</string>
	    <string _locid="250500">Champion Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="250501">Warrior Priestess attack and hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="250502">Champion Warrior Priestess</string>
	    <string _locid="250503">Legendary Warrior Priestesses</string>
	    <string _locid="250504">Warrior Priestess attack and hitpoints increased.</string>
	    <string _locid="250505">Legendary Warrior Priestess</string>
	    <string _locid="250750">Willaq Umu Support</string>
	    <string _locid="250751">The Willaq Umu sends 9 Warrior Priestesses and increases their hitpoints.</string>
	    <string _locid="250752">Willaq Umu Support Shipment has arrived.</string>
	    <string _locid="250999">4 Macemen</string>
	</Language>
  </StringTable>
</stringmods>
